<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Suchinton&#39;s Hub 🚀</title>
    <link>https://suchinton.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Suchinton&#39;s Hub 🚀</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://suchinton.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GSoC Community Bonding Period</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/community-bonding-period/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/community-bonding-period/</guid>
      <description># Topics to be covered in this post  What is the Community bonding period? What I did the past month Challenges faced Community interactions What I plan to do next   What is GSoC and what have I been up to during the CBP? Google Summer of Code (GSoC) is a global program that offers students an opportunity to contribute to open-source projects. The program is sponsored by Google and has been running since 2005.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Semester-long Intern at FOSSEE, IIT Bombay (February - May 2023)</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/portfolio/fossee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/portfolio/fossee/</guid>
      <description>What is FOSSEE? FOSSEE is a project developed at IIT Bombay that promotes the use of FLOSS tools in academia and research. The project is funded by the National Mission on Education through ICT, Ministry of Education, Government of India. FOSSEE supports various FLOSS tools such as Scilab, Python, eSim, OpenFOAM, DWSIM, R, OpenModelica and more.
My work   Flatpak_Test_App (FOSSEE_Installer_Test): A proof of concept application, implemented using Qt5 and Flatpak Sandboxing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Suchinton Chakravarty Linux Enthusiast GSoC &#39;23 @ AGL eSim-intern 2023, IIT Bombay  I am a 4th-year student at Amity University Noida, pursuing a B.Tech degree in Computer Science &amp;amp; Engineering. I am passionate about Linux and open-source software and love to tinker with new technologies and learn new things whenever I can.
Currently, I am a contributor to GSoC &amp;lsquo;23 at AGL under The Linux Foundation, and working on implementing a Qt5 application that can simulate CAN Bus signals using Kuksa.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
