<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Suchinton&#39;s Hub 🚀</title>
    <link>https://suchinton.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Suchinton&#39;s Hub 🚀</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 14:34:21 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://suchinton.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 20 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 14:34:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-20/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Pushing code to Gerrit. Added drop-down in settings to pick configs. Refactored config.py and settings.py to handle user preferences better.   What I plan to do next   # Pushing to Gerrit This week, major work was completed for the AGL Demo Control Panel and commits were made for review on Gerrit. The following changes have been pushed so far:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 19 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 16:13:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-19/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Pushing code to Gerrit. Refactor acceleration and script for IC page. Add compatibility for Databroker.   What I plan to do next   # Pushing to Gerrit This week, major work was completed for the AGL Demo Control Panel and commits were made for review on Gerrit. The following changes have been pushed so far:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 18 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 14:39:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-18/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Pushing code to Gerrit. Simplified settings page. Add compatibility for Databroker. Refactor acceleration and script for IC page.   What I plan to do next   # Pushing to Gerrit This week saw major documentation work for the AGL Demo Control Panel and partial commits were made for review on Gerrit.
Changes pushed so far:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 17 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 16:57:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-17/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Pushing code to Gerrit. Fixing scaling of Dashboard icons. Completed initial draft of documentation.   What I plan to do next   # Pushing to Gerrit This week saw major documentation work for the AGL Demo Control Panel and partial commits were made for review on Gerrit.
Changes pushed so far:
 29237: Update UI files | https://gerrit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 16 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-16/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Pushed partial code to Gerrit for review. Completed initial documentation. Resolved minor bugs and UI tweaks. Refactored code wherever needed.   What I plan to do next   # Pushing code to Gerrit This week saw major refactoring and documentation of the code for the AGL Demo Control Panel and partial commits were made for review on Gerrit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 15 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-15/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  First draft of the &amp;ldquo;AGL Demo Control Panel&amp;rdquo; documentation.  Minor Adjustments to UI Simplified Settings Page. Refactoring the VSS subscription Module   What I plan to do next   # First draft of the &amp;ldquo;AGL Demo Control Panel&amp;rdquo; documentation.  I started writing the initial draft of the documentation for AGL Demo Control Panel by following the steps provided in the official documentation of AGL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 14 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-14/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Enabled Secure Mode Switched to Carbon icons. Animated Navigation of Control Panel   What I plan to do next   # Enable Secure Mode Till now, our testing of the AGL Demo Control Panel was being conducted in Insecure mode, i.e. SSL encryption was disabled when connecting to the server (had to run both with the --insecure flag).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 13 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-13/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Subscribe to VSS signals for registering changes made on target. Refactored the toggle inputs as animated switches. Start working with Kuksa-client 0.4.0   What I plan to do next   # Subscribing to VSS signals This week I added support for subscribing to VSS Signals for the IC and HVAC Pages such that any changes made to their values through a different interface will now also be reflected on the Control Panel without delay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 12 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-12/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Created CAN interface using cannelloni Implemented the FeedCAN module. Added support for sending Steering wheel CAN messages. Created a test script for sending CAN frames using the USB CAN adapter.   What I plan to do next   # How to use cannelloni To test the AGL Demo Control Panel for sending CAN messages to the target machine, we can create a virtual CAN interface using cannelloni.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 11 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-11/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Tested the USB CAN adapters with hlcand on Raspberry Pi OS and PC. Minor UI changes changed the default font to ttf-Dejavu.   What I plan to do next   # Testing USB CAN Adapters Resources used,  hlcand USB to CAN Analyzer Adapter can-utils Raspberry Pi 4 (Raspberry Pi OS) PC (Ubuntu 22.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 10 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-10/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Resolved the assets licenses and removed unused assets (icons). Fixed the window resizing issue. Increased the navigation button sizes. Added toggle button to switch between kuksa to CAN signals for Steering wheel controls   What I plan to do next   # Assets This week I resolved licenses for the various assets used in the project,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 9 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-9/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Refined the navigation bar Improved Acceleration function Dummy triggers for Steering Wheel controls   What I plan to do next   # Navigation Bar This week I switched the navigation bar from a vertical layout to a horizontal layout to make navigation more intuitive and accessible. I am currently working on revising the animation of the button sizes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 8 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-8/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Uploaded the repo to Gerrit as a patch set, link. Deprecated Navigation Page after discussion with mentors. Refactored QThread instance for feeding values to the kuksa server. Added option in settings to hide pages. Reviewed documentation for Python-can to enable Steering wheel controls.   What I plan to do next   # Pushing To Gerrit I was able to push all of my progress to Gerrit this week despite a few challenges, where every time I would try to clone the agl-demo-control-panel repo, I would get the following message:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 7 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-7/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Finalized Steering Wheel Layout Tested AGL_Control_Panel against AGL image on RPi 4 Added Installation script for Ubuntu/ Debian   What I plan to do next   # Finalized Steering Wheel Layout This week I was able to finalize the layout and VSS paths to be used for the Steering Wheel Page, this shall remain subject to further improvements and revisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 6 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-6/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Specified Steering wheel Controls Improved Settings page and error handling Default settings Improved Navigation Page Updated README and Troubleshooting steps   What I plan to do next   # Steering Wheel Controls This week I added the various signals for the Steering Wheel Controls, namely
 Volume Up: &amp;ldquo;Vehicle.Cabin.SteeringWheel.Switches.VolumeUp&amp;rdquo; Volume Down: &amp;ldquo;Vehicle.Cabin.SteeringWheel.Switches.VolumeDown&amp;rdquo; Volume Mute: &amp;ldquo;Vehicle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 5 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-5/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Refactored the IC Acceleration function IC page script (Toggle) Initialized Steering wheel Signals Controls (Not yet functional) Navigation Page (Revised Style sheet and improved operations   What I plan to do next   # IC Acceleration Button This week I updated the Acceleration button to operate on a Pressed and Released event instead of the previously used Clicked event, this allows us to implement a both Acceleration and Deceliration proportionally for the vehicle&amp;rsquo;s Speed and the Engine RPM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 4 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-4/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Added HVAC signals, limited to 4 Toggle for Secure and Insecure Mode Added animations for navigation and improved window handles New theme for UI Reading from the config file   What I plan to do next   # HVAC signals This week I started adding signal inputs for the HVAC page, currently only 4 VIS signals are supported as the demo apps have not been patched to support other signals and mostly unresponsive on the Qt5 &amp;amp; Flutter images of AGL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 3 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-3/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Added Settings Window to main Application Completed Support for IC Application Signals Added custom handles for window Uploaded GitHub Readme.md Building AGL-demo-platform Image   What I plan to do next   # AGL-Demo-Control-Panel Added Settings Window to main Application The settings window provides various options to configure the kuksa-client. functionalities are:
 Start Connection Create Network Bridge Reconnect Refresh Input IP Address Input JWT Token Path for Authorization Display Connection Status  IC Kuksa Signals This week I improved the style sheet for the IC page to better integrate with the application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 2 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-2/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Implement Settings Window Initial support for Kuksa Signals Initializing the GitHub Repository   What I plan to do next   # Settings Window This week I implemented the settings window to start/ configure an instance of kuksa-client to be used across the whole application. Features of this module are as follows:
 Configure Kuksa-client  Custom IP address JWT token path Toggle for Insecure mode   Start/ Reconnect Kuksa-client Display Connection Status  How Does it Work?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 1 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-1/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Communication with Kuksa.val Skeleton code for GUI using PyQt5 Navigation widget for IC   What I plan to do next   # Communication With Kuksa.val Continuing with the progress made last week regarding communication with Kuksa-val-server using a bridged network, I tried to enable IP routing to make the traffic at 10.10.10.204 also accessible at localhost 127.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSoC Community Bonding Period</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/community-bonding-period/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/community-bonding-period/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What is the Community bonding period? What I did the past month Challenges faced Community interactions What I plan to do next   What is GSoC &amp;amp; What Have I Been Up To During The CBP? Google Summer of Code (GSoC) is a global program that offers students an opportunity to contribute to open-source projects. The program is sponsored by Google and has been running since 2005.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Semester-long Intern at FOSSEE, IIT Bombay (February - May 2023)</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/portfolio/fossee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/portfolio/fossee/</guid>
      <description>What is FOSSEE? FOSSEE is a project developed at IIT Bombay that promotes the use of FLOSS tools in academia and research. The project is funded by the National Mission on Education through ICT, Ministry of Education, Government of India. FOSSEE supports various FLOSS tools such as Scilab, Python, eSim, OpenFOAM, DWSIM, R, OpenModelica and more.
My work   Flatpak_Test_App (FOSSEE_Installer_Test): A proof of concept application, implemented using Qt5 and Flatpak Sandboxing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Suchinton Chakravarty Linux Enthusiast GSoC &#39;23 @ AGL eSim-intern 2023, IIT Bombay  I am a 4th-year student at Amity University Noida, pursuing a B.Tech degree in Computer Science &amp;amp; Engineering. I am passionate about Linux and open-source software and love to tinker with new technologies and learn new things whenever I can.
Currently, I am a contributor to GSoC &amp;lsquo;23 at AGL under The Linux Foundation, and working on implementing a Qt5 application that can simulate CAN Bus signals using Kuksa.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
