<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GSoC &#39;23 Blog on Suchinton&#39;s Hub 🚀</title>
    <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GSoC &#39;23 Blog on Suchinton&#39;s Hub 🚀</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://suchinton.github.io/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 7 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-7/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Finalized Steering Wheel Layout Tested AGL_Control_Panel against AGL image on RPi 4 Added Installation script for Ubuntu/ Debian   What I plan to do next   # Finalized Steering Wheel Layout This week I was able to finalize the layout and VSS paths to be used for the Steering Wheel Page, this shall remain subject to further improvements and revisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 6 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-6/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Specified Steering wheel Controls Improved Settings page and error handling Default settings Improved Navigation Page Updated README and Troubleshooting steps   What I plan to do next   # Steering Wheel Controls This week I added the various signals for the Steering Wheel Controls, namely
 Volume Up: &amp;ldquo;Vehicle.Cabin.SteeringWheel.Switches.VolumeUp&amp;rdquo; Volume Down: &amp;ldquo;Vehicle.Cabin.SteeringWheel.Switches.VolumeDown&amp;rdquo; Volume Mute: &amp;ldquo;Vehicle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 5 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-5/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Refactored the IC Acceleration function IC page script (Toggle) Initialized Steering wheel Signals Controls (Not yet functional) Navigation Page (Revised Style sheet and improved operations   What I plan to do next   # IC Acceleration Button This week I updated the Acceleration button to operate on a Pressed and Released event instead of the previously used Clicked event, this allows us to implement a both Acceleration and Deceliration proportionally for the vehicle&amp;rsquo;s Speed and the Engine RPM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 4 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-4/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Added HVAC signals, limited to 4 Toggle for Secure and Insecure Mode Added animations for navigation and improved window handles New theme for UI Reading from the config file   What I plan to do next   # HVAC signals This week I started adding signal inputs for the HVAC page, currently only 4 VIS signals are supported as the demo apps have not been patched to support other signals and mostly unresponsive on the Qt5 &amp;amp; Flutter images of AGL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 3 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-3/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Added Settings Window to main Application Completed Support for IC Application Signals Added custom handles for window Uploaded GitHub Readme.md Building AGL-demo-platform Image   What I plan to do next   # AGL-Demo-Control-Panel Added Settings Window to main Application The settings window provides various options to configure the kuksa-client. functionalities are:
 Start Connection Create Network Bridge Reconnect Refresh Input IP Address Input JWT Token Path for Authorization Display Connection Status  IC Kuksa Signals This week I improved the style sheet for the IC page to better integrate with the application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 2 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-2/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Implement Settings Window Initial support for Kuksa Signals Initializing the GitHub Repository   What I plan to do next   # Settings Window This week I implemented the settings window to start/ configure an instance of kuksa-client to be used across the whole application. Features of this module are as follows:
 Configure Kuksa-client  Custom IP address JWT token path Toggle for Insecure mode   Start/ Reconnect Kuksa-client Display Connection Status  How Does it Work?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 1 Progress Report</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/week-1/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What I did this week  Communication with Kuksa.val Skeleton code for GUI using PyQt5 Navigation widget for IC   What I plan to do next   # Communication With Kuksa.val Continuing with the progress made last week regarding communication with Kuksa-val-server using a bridged network, I tried to enable IP routing to make the traffic at 10.10.10.204 also accessible at localhost 127.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSoC Community Bonding Period</title>
      <link>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/community-bonding-period/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://suchinton.github.io/articles/community-bonding-period/</guid>
      <description># Topics To Be Covered In This Post  What is the Community bonding period? What I did the past month Challenges faced Community interactions What I plan to do next   What is GSoC &amp;amp; What Have I Been Up To During The CBP? Google Summer of Code (GSoC) is a global program that offers students an opportunity to contribute to open-source projects. The program is sponsored by Google and has been running since 2005.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
